boilerguide.co.uk 2012-10-29

# Privacy

This website is brought to you by Holmes Media (UK) Limited (herein after referred to as “the Company”). We take the privacy of our website users very seriously. We ask that you read this Privacy Policy (“the Policy”) carefully as it contains important information about how we will use your personal data. 

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, the Company (“we” or “us”) is the ‘Data Controller’ i.e. the company who is responsible for, and controls the processing of, your personal data). 

This Policy does not apply to other websites linked through this website. Personal information which you choose to provide to other websites will be subject to the Privacy Policy of each of those websites which we urge you to check prior to disclosing further information to them. 

## Personal Data we may collect about you

We will obtain personal data about you (such as your name, address, payment details, opinions etc.) whenever you complete an online form. 

For example, we will obtain your personal data when you register to use this website, send us feedback, contact us for any reason, sign up to a service, request a quotation, enter a competition, purchase goods or services. We may also obtain sensitive personal data about you if you volunteer it during the completion of an online form. If you volunteer such information you will be consenting to our processing it for the purposes specified. If no such purposes are specified please contact us immediately and we will be happy to specify these for your information. 

We will also collect personal information that you provide us through the use of the “Get Quote” feature. This personally identifiable data is passed on to third parties that meet the criteria you have chosen, for example, if you request a quote for a new central heating system we will pass your personal details on to all suppliers signed up to our service who can fulfil your request. 

We may monitor your usage of this website. This may include monitoring how many times you visit, which pages you go to, traffic data, location data and the originating domain name of a users internet service provider. This information helps us to build a profile of our users. Some of this data will be aggregated or statistical, which means that we will not be able to identify you individually. In this regard, please also see the further section on ‘ **Use of cookies** ’ below. 

Occasionally we may receive information about you from other sources (such as credit reference agencies) which we will add to the information which we already hold about you in order to help us to provide you with goods and services and to improve and personalise our service to you. 

## How we may use your personal data

We will not use or disclose your personal information unless you have given your permission, except for the following purposes:- 

  1. To assist, operate and improve this website and the services provided through it.
  2. To keep you informed about us and our services.
  3. To fulfil the “Get Quote” service which requires us to pass your details on to third parties suppliers signed up to our service.
  4. Administration and statistical analysis.
  5. Fraud prevention and detection and to the extent that we are required to disclose such personal information by any rule of law, regulation or legal process.
  6. Billing and order fulfilment security vetting.

## Marketing and opting out

We may share your personal data with organisations who are our business partners and we or they may contact you, unless you have asked us or them not to do so, by e-mail, letter or telephone about products, services, promotions or special offers which may be of interest to you. 

If you prefer not to receive any further marketing communications from us, you can opt out at any time. See below for further information. 

## Disclosure of your personal data

We may disclose your personal data to:- 

  1. Other companies within our group.
  2. Our agents and services providers who will be carefully chosen, reputable and trustworthy. We will follow the relevant legal requirements and use all reasonable precautions to ensure that only responsible third parties see you personal information. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or act or omission of the third parties who receive the personal information.
  3. Credit reference agencies.
  4. Law enforcement agencies in connection with any investigation and those requiring it to help prevent unlawful activity.
  5. Our business partners in accordance with the ‘ **Marketing and opting out** ’ section above.

Whilst we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal data, you acknowledge that the use of the internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal data which is transferred from you or to you via the internet. 

## Information about other individuals

If you give us information on behalf of someone else, you confirm that the other person has appointed you to act on his/her behalf and has agreed that you can:- 

  1. Give consent on his/her behalf to the processing of his/her personal data.
  2. Receive on his/her behalf any data protection notices.
  3. Give consent to the transfer of his/her personal data abroad.

## Use of cookies

When you use this website we may collect information about your computer, such as your IP address and/or information about you browser, which we will use for administration purposes and statistical analysis. This information will not usually identify you personally. 

We may also obtain information about your online movements and use of the internet. We do this by placing a ‘cookie’, which is a small file, on your computers hard disk. Cookies are used for several reasons:- 

  1. To recognise you whenever you visit this website.
  2. To speed up access to this website (so you do not have to log in each time).
  3. To store your personal preferences.
  4. To build a profile about you.
  5. To better understand the relevant marketing and advertising opportunities relevant to you.
  6. Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet.
  7. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your previous visits to this website or another website owned by the Company.
  8. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/) or via the the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) for third party vendors.

The vast majority of web browsers accept cookies. However, you can change your browser settings so that cookies are not accepted. If you do this, you may lose some of the functionality of this website. 

## Your rights

You have the right, subject to the payment of a small fee (currently £10.00) to request access to your personal data which we may process about you. If you wish to exercise this right you should:- 

  1. Put your request in writing.
  2. Include proof of your identity and address (e.g. copy of your driving license or passport, and a recent utility or credit card bill)
  3. Attach a cheque in the amount of £10.00 made payable to ‘Holmes Media (UK) Ltd’.
  4. Specify the personal data you want access to including any account or reference numbers where applicable.

You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge. If you do wish to exercise this right you should:- 

  1. Put your request in writing.
  2. Provide us with enough information to identify you (e.g. account number, user name, registration details).
  3. Specify the information that is incorrect and what it should be replaced with.

You also have the right to ask us to stop processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. If you wish to exercise this right you should:- 

  1. Put your request in writing via the contact form
  2. Provide us with enough information to identify you (e.g. account number, user name, registration details).
  3. If your objection is not to direct marketing in general, but to direct marketing by a particular channel (e.g. e-mail or telephone) please specify the channel you are objecting to.

## Our contact details

We welcome your feedback and questions. If you wish to contact us, please do so via the contact form or you can write to us at Boiler Guide, c/o Holmes Media (UK) Limited, 11 The Point, Rockingham Road, Market Harborough, LE16 7QU, or you may call us on 0845 287 5939. Registered in England No. 6873930 Vat No. 904 1556 46. 

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. You should check this policy occasionally to ensure you’re aware of the most recent version which will apply each time you access this website.
